Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES IV. Subject Files, 1928-1980
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES IV. SUBJECT FILES
  - Conferences
    - Population Growth, "A Medical Responsibility," Symposium, Palm Springs, Nov., 1964 (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - Postpartum Family Planning Program Meeting, New York City, September 11-13, 1967 (Box 109, Folder 15)
    - PPWP Public Affairs Conference 1973 (Box 109, Folder 16)
    - Pugwash Conference on the Population Problem, Sinai, Rumania, August 26-31, 1971 (Box 109, Folder 17)
    - Reproductive Freedom Project, Conferences, ACLU 1974 (Box 109, Folder 18)
    - Searle Conference 1965 (Box 109, Folder 19)
    - Spring Hill Conference on Future Alternatives on Population and Family Planning in the U.S. 1973-74 (Box 109, Folder 20)
    - Southwest Regional Conference, Child Welfare League of America 1969-70 (Box 109, Folder 21)
    - Spring Post Graduate Conference, Emory University School of Medicine 1971-72 (Box 109, Folder 22)
    - A Statewide Conference for Nursing Educators on Family Planning 1969-70 (Box 109, Folder 23)
    - United Nations Conference on the Human Environment, Stockholm 1971-72 (Box 109, Folder 24)
    - U.N. World Population Conference
      - Belgrade, Yugoslavia 1965-67 (Box 109, Folder 25)
      - Bucharest, Folk Arts Seminar/Workshop Exhibit on Population Communication and Education 1974 (Box 109, Folder 26)
      - Bucharest 1973-74 (Box 109, Folder 27)
      - Population Tribune, Non-Government Forum, World Population Conference, Bucharest 1973-74 (Box 109, Folder 28)
      - Conference on World Population Year, 1974, Non-Government Organizations, U.S. Government Department of State, 6/27/74 (Box 109, Folder 29)
    - University of Chicago Conference Information, Communication, Components of FP Programs in the 1970's, 1971 (Box 109, Folder 30)
    - Young World Development Conference, Aspen, Colorado 1971 (Box 109, Folder 31)
    - Conferences, miscellaneous
      - 1966-72 (Box 109, Folder 32)
      - 1975-78 (Box 109)
    - Conferences, miscellaneous, general 1962-72 (Box 109, Folder 33)
    - Out-card/file White House Conferences (Box 109, Folder 34)
  - Contraceptives
    - General
      - Birth Control, Methods, general correspondence
        - 1955-74 (Box 109, Folder 35)
        - 1975 (Box 109)
      - Birth Control, Methods, General, Booklets, Mimeos 1955-65 (Box 109, Folder 36)
      - Contraceptives, Contraceptive Advertising, Code Authority, National Association Broadcasters 1975-78 (Box 109, Folder 37)
    - Condoms
      - 1971-74 (Box 109, Folder 38)
      - 1975-79 (Box 109)
      - Battelle Condom Conference Project 1973-74 (Box 109, Folder 39)
    - Diaphragm
      - Contraceptives, Diaphragm 1954-75 (Box 109, Folder 40)
      - Contraceptives, Food and Drug Administration Regulations 1958-62 (Box 109, Folder 41)
    - Intrauterine Devices
      - General Correspondence (Box 109)
        - 1961-74 (Box 109, Folder 42)
        - 1975-76 (Box 109)
        - 1962-74 (Box 109, Folder 43)
        - 1975 (Box 109)
      - IUCD Conference
        - Lubbock, Texas, August 28, 1965 (Box 109, Folder 44)
        - Alabama 1964-67 (Box 109, Folder 45)
      - Intrauterine Devices, Film, correspondence 1962-65 (Box 109, Folder 46)
    - Contraceptives, Jelly 1957-58 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Oral
      - Birth Control, Pills 1957-60 (Box 110, Folder 2)
      - Contraceptives, Oral, Miscellaneous Material
        - 1960-74 (Box 110, Folder 3)
        - 1975-77 (Box 110)
      - Contraceptives, Oral, general correspondence
        - 1964-74 (Box 110, Folder 4)
        - 1975-76 (Box 110)
    - Research
      - Contraceptives Research, general
        - 1969-74 (Box 110, Folder 5)
        - 1975-78 (Box 110)
      - Contraceptive Research, National Institute of Child Health and Human Development 1970 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Birth Control, Methods, Rhythm, correspondence 1959-71 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Sterilization
      - Sterilization, correspondence
        - 1960-74 (Box 110, Folder 8)
        - 1975-79 (Box 110)
      - Sterilization, general
        - 1974 (Box 110, Folder 9)
        - 1975-79 (Box 110)
        - 1970-73 (Box 110, Folder 10)
        - 1946-69 (Box 110, Folder 11)
      - Sterilization, Research 1978 (Box 110, Folder 12)
      - Vasectomy 1954-72 (Box 110, Folder 13)
      - Contraceptives, Research, Sterilization, Chemical, Vasectomy 1979, undated (Box 110, Folder 14)
      - Steroids, correspondence 1955-58 (Box 110, Folder 15)
      - Steroids, Conference and Related Data 1957-58 (Box 110, Folder 16)
  - Contracts
    - 1970-74 (Box 110, Folder 17)
    - 1975-80 (Box 110)
    - Contracts, Consultants Contracts 1977-78 (Box 110, Folder 18)
    - Contracts, correspondence
      - 1971-74 (Box 110, Folder 19)
      - 1975-79 (Box 110)
    - Contracts, HSA 105-74-208-DHEW- I&E Publications Contract (Box 110)
      - 1974 (Box 110, Folder 20)
      - 1975-78 (Box 110)
    - Contracts, Marvel Comics 1975 (Box 110, Folder 21)
    - Contracts, Vision Associates 1970 (Box 110, Folder 22)
  - Coo, Misc. 1956-66 (Box 110, Folder 23)
  - Copeland, Lammot DUP 1962-69 (Box 110, Folder 24)
  - Copyrights
    - 1965-74 (Box 110, Folder 25)
    - 1975-78 (Box 110)
  - Cou, Misc. 1960-68 (Box 110, Folder 26)
  - Cowles, John 1955-61 (Box 110, Folder 27)
  - Cr, Misc. 1955-69 (Box 110, Folder 28)
  - Crank Letters, General 1957-73 (Box 110, Folder 29)
  - Cu, Misc. 1961-68 (Box 110, Folder 30)
  - Cushman, Howard 1956-66 (Box 110, Folder 31)
  - D, Misc. 1961-71 (Box 110, Folder 32)
  - Davis, Dr. Kingsley 1955-61 (Box 110, Folder 33)
  - De, Misc. 1961-71 (Box 110, Folder 34)
  - Deans of Schools of Social Work, Questionnaire 1962-66 (Box 110, Folder 35)
  - De Vilbiss, Dr. Lydia Allen 1969-60 (Box 110, Folder 36)
  - Devin-Adair Company 1965 (Box 110, Folder 37)
  - Di, Misc. 1966-67 (Box 110, Folder 38)
  - Dickenson, Robert Latou, M.D. 1961 (Box 110, Folder 39)
  - Do, Misc. 1962-69 (Box 110, Folder 40)
  - Doubleday and Company, Correspondence 1955-67 (Box 110, Folder 41)
  - Dr, Misc.
    - 1965-74 (Box 110, Folder 42)
    - 1975-79 (Box 110)
  - Draper, Gen. Wm. H.
    - Correspondence 1960-63 (Box 110, Folder 43)
    - General, Misc., Speeches 1961-63 (Box 110, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence 1964-73 (Box 110, Folder 45)
  - Du, Misc.
    - 1963-74 (Box 110, Folder 46)
    - 1975-79 (Box 110)
  - E, Misc. 1964-69 (Box 110, Folder 47)
  - Eccles, Marriner S., correspondence 1966-72 (Box 110, Folder 48)
  - Education
    - Population Education
      - 1970-74 (Box 111, Folder 1)
      - 1975-77 (Box 111)
    - Population Education 1965 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Population Education, PP of Maryland, Baltimore Public Schools, Conn. Demographic Council 1971 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Maryland, Workshop on Population, Education in Secondary Schools 1970 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Sex Education
      - 1970-74 (Box 111, Folder 5)
      - 1975-79 (Box 111, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence 1962-69 (Box 111, Folder 6)
      - General, Literature
        - 1960-74 (Box 111, Folder 7)
        - 1975-79 (Box 111)
      - Summary of Sex Education Project Conducted 1977-78(Carrera) (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D., Letters to Eisenhower regarding Gruening Committee 1965 (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - El-Em, Misc. 1955-66 (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Eli Lilly and Company, correspondence 1964-70 (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Emerson Books, Inc. 1955-66 (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Emko, Correspondence
    - 1962-74 (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - 1975-77 (Box 111)
    - 1959-71 (Box 111, Folder 14-15)
  - En, Misc. 1964-69 (Box 111, Folder 16)
  - Encyclopedia
    - "Britannica Book of the Year," 1955-68 (Box 111, Folder 17)
    - "World Scope,"1955-66 (Box 111, Folder 18)
  - Encyclopedia and Directories, General 1954-70 (Box 111, Folder 19)
  - Technical Assistance, Clearing House, Correspondence 1963 (Box 111, Folder 20)
  - Endorsements, List of 1000 Organizations before 1935, 1926-64 (Box 111, Folder 21)
  - English, O. Spurgeon 1956-57 (Box 111, Folder 22)
  - Enke, Stephen, Correspondence 1965-69 (Box 111, Folder 23)
  - Enovid
    - Correspondence 1963-66 (Box 111, Folder 24-29)
    - re: N.D.A. 10976, Development of Thrombosis while on Cyclic Medication, G. D. Searle and Co., 12/20/61 (Box 111, Folder 30)
    - Cases of Thrombophlebitis, August 10, 1962 (Box 111, Folder 31)
    - Individual Requests for Information 1960-65 (Box 111, Folder 32)
    - Packaging, correspondence 1960-66 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Reprints, New Items 1960-65 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Environment from 1970-71 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, ERA
    - 1973-74 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - 1975-78 (Box 112)
  - Er, Misc. 1964-73 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Exhibits
    - General Correspondence
      - 1970-74 (Box 112, Folder 6)
      - 1975-77 (Box 112)
      - 1969-55 (Box 112, Folder 7-8)
    - "Consensus"
      - Correspondence 1960-64 (Box 112, Folder 9)
      - Episcopal Convention, Detroit, Mich., Sept. 1961 (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - "Impact of New Methods," 1963-64 (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - New England Health Institute, correspondence 1958-64 (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - Scientific and Medical, correspondence 1963 (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - Ideas for 1955 Exhibit, "Help for the Childless," undated (Box 112, Folder 14)
    - Scientific and Medical 1961-62 (Box 112, Folder 15)
    - World's Fair
      - Correspondence 1962-67 (Box 112, Folder 16)
      - Mimeos and Misc. Material 1964-67 (Box 112, Folder 17)
  - F, Misc. 1964-68 (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - Fact Book by: Joseph Jones 1961-64 (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Fagley, Richard M. 1955-67 (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - Family Planning
    - Correspondence and general 1957-69 (Box 112, Folder 21)
    - Coercion
      - 1969-70 (Box 112, Folder 22)
      - 1975-79 (Box 112)
    - Voluntarism 1969 (empty) (Box 112, Folder 23)
    - Organizational Statements, re: Family Planning 1960-68 (Box 112, Folder 24)
  - Faulkner, Mrs. James (Mary)
    - 1971-74 (Box 112, Folder 25)
    - 1978 (Box 112)
  - Ferguson, Robert M., Mrs. 1954-73 (Box 112, Folder 26-27)
  - Fi, Misc. 1961-69 (Box 112, Folder 28)
  - Films
    - General Correspondence
      - 1968-74 (Box 112, Folder 29)
      - 1975-80 (Box 112)
      - 1959-68 (Box 112, Folder 30-32)
    - ABT Associates, correspondence 1969 (Box 112, Folder 33)
    - Association Films, Correspondence 1959-67 (Box 112, Folder 34)
    - "Beyond Conception" (Dr. Geo. Denniston) 1968 (Box 112, Folder 35)
    - Churchill Films, correspondence 1966-68 (Box 112, Folder 36)
    - About PP, General Listing and Correspondence 1960-67 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - PPWP Library, Contemporary Films, General Correspondence 1966-72 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Parthenon Pictures
      - Correspondence 1959-69 (Box 113, Folder 3-5)
      - General 1959-64 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Peerles Film Processing Corp. 1963-66 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Visual Projects, Newton E. Meltzer 1961-68 (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - PPWP Films
      - Films, Medical, Teaching, Financial Arrangements 1964-67 (Box 113, Folder 9)
      - Commonwealth Fund, Medical Teaching Film
        - Advisory Council 1964 (Box 113, Folder 10)
        - Correspondence 1963-66 (Box 113, Folder 11)
        - Screening, July 16, 1965 (Box 113, Folder 12)
        - Distribution 1965-66 (Box 113, Folder 13)
        - The Rockefeller Foundation, Medical Teaching Film, Translations 1965 (Box 113, Folder 14)
        - Translations and Public Affairs C. 1965-66 (Box 113, Folder 15)
        - Herman Engel 1964-66 (Box 113, Folder 16)
      - Medical Teaching Films on Contraception
        - General from 1964-68 (Box 113, Folder 17)
        - Bids, General 1963-1964 (Box 113, Folder 18)
        - Correspondence 1963-67 (Box 113, Folder 19)
        - Medical Teaching Film Script, Alan F. Guttmacher, M.D. 1964 (Box 113, Folder 20)
    - Films, About PP
      - "Before They Say I Do" from 1961-64 (Box 113, Folder 21)
      - "The Costly Crowd," Correspondence 1961-65 (Box 113, Folder 22)
      - "Fair Chance," General from 1959-60 (Box 113, Folder 23)
    - Films, Spanish Language, Vugie Productions
      - Reports, Misc. 1964-66 (Box 113, Folder 24)
      - General 1964-69 (Box 113, Folder 25)
    - U.S. Productions 1962-64 (Box 113, Folder 26)
    - Films, General, Correspondence, Misc. from 1955-80 (Box 113, Folder 27)
  - Fl, Misc. 1960-67 (Box 113, Folder 28)
  - Fo, Misc.
    - 1964-74 (Box 113, Folder 29)
    - 1975-79 (Box 113)
  - Foundations, Funds and Trusts
    - Foundations and Funds, A 1963-74 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - ARCA Foundation
      - 1968-74 (Box 114, Folder 2)
      - 1975 (Box 114)
    - Asia Foundation 1955, 1960, 1966, undated (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Avalon Foundation, correspondence 1968-71 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Foundations and Funds, B
      - 1963-74 (Box 114, Folder 5)
      - 1975-77 (Box 114)
    - Babcock (Mary Reynolds) Foundation, Inc. 1961-74 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Baker (The George F.) Trust 1938, 1948-70 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Dr. Anna Bartsch-Dunne Fund for Research
      - 1972-74 (Box 114, Folder 8)
      - 1975 (Box 114)
    - The Bass Foundation
      - 1972-74 (Box 114, Folder 9)
      - 1975-76 (Box 114)
    - Booth-Ferris Foundation 1965 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - The Brush Foundation
      - 1969-74 (Box 114, Folder 11)
      - 1975-77 (Box 114)
    - Foundations and Funds, C
      - 1965-74 (Box 114, Folder 12)
      - 1975-78 (Box 114)
    - Calder (Louis) Foundation 1969 (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Carolyn Foundation
      - 1971-74 (Box 114, Folder 14)
      - 1975-78 (Box 114)
    - Cary (Mary Flagler) Charitable Trust 1972-74 (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - Chichester Du Pont Foundation, Inc. 1964-74 (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - Clark (Edna McConnell) Foundation 1971-74 (Box 114, Folder 17)
    - Commonwealth Fund, Correspondence
      - 1963-74 (Box 114, Folder 18)
      - 1975-78 (Box 114)
    - Council of Foundations Annual Meeting, F.S. Jaffe Presentation, San Antonio 1974 (Box 114, Folder 19)
    - Foundations and Funds, D 1961-72 (Box 114, Folder 20)
    - Davis (The Arthur Vining) Foundation 1971-72 (Box 114, Folder 21)
    - Foundations and Funds, E
      - 1968-74 (Box 114, Folder 22)
      - 1975-79 (Box 114)
    - Eastman (Lucius and Eva) Fund 1967 (Box 114, Folder 23)
    - Eisenhower Memorial Fund 1969-72 (Box 114, Folder 24)
    - Foundations and Funds, F 1961-68 (Box 114, Folder 25)
    - Family Life Education from 1956-60 (Box 114, Folder 26)
    - Foundation, Fels, Correspondence 1966-69 (Box 114, Folder 27)
    - Foundations, Ford
      - Correspondence
        - 1967-74 (Box 114, Folder 28)
        - 1975-77 (Box 114)
        - 1963-66 (Box 114, Folder 29)
      - General 1962-74 (Box 114, Folder 30)
      - Report to the Ford Foundation on the Project Development Program 1968 (Box 114, Folder 31)
    - Foundation News Reprints 1974-75 (Box 114, Folder 32)
    - Fund for the Republic 1958-65 (Box 114, Folder 33)
    - Foundations and Funds, G 1967-74 (Box 114, Folder 34)
    - General Service Foundation [Musser]
      - 1969-74 (Box 114, Folder 35)
      - 1975-78 (Box 114)
    - Gould (Edwin) Foundation for Children 1966-69 (Box 114, Folder 36)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Foundation 1955-58 (Box 114, Folder 37)
    - Gund Foundation
      - 1971-74 (Box 114, Folder 38)
      - 1975-76 (Box 114)
    - Alan F. Guttmacher Memorial Fund 1974 (Box 114, Folder 39)
    - Foundations and Funds, H
      - 1970-74 (Box 114, Folder 40)
      - 1975-76 (Box 114)
    - Halsell (Ewing) Foundation 1968-74 (Box 114, Folder 41)
    - Henderson (A.D.) Foundation 1973 (Box 114, Folder 42)
    - The Huber Foundation
      - 1961-74 (Box 114, Folder 43)
      - 1975-77 (Box 114)
    - Foundations and Funds, I
      - 1971-74 (Box 114, Folder 44)
      - 1975 (Box 114)
    - Ittelson Family Foundation 1958-73 (Box 114, Folder 45)
    - Foundations and Funds, J 1967-70 (Box 114, Folder 46)
    - Johnson (The Robert Wood) Foundation 1971-74 (Box 114, Folder 47)
    - Foundations and Funds, K
      - 1966-74 (Box 114, Folder 48)
      - 1975-78 (Box 114)
    - Foundations, Kellogg, Correspondence, Misc.
      - 1967-74 (Box 114, Folder 49)
      - 1975-78 (Box 114)
    - Foundations, Kellogg Technical Assistance Program, the "Center," Correspondence 1968 (Box 114, Folder 50)
    - The Kennedy (Joseph P., Jr.) Foundation 1977 (Box 114, Folder 51)
    - Foundations and Funds, L
      - 1963-74 (Box 114, Folder 52)
      - 1975 (Box 114)
    - Lasker Foundation, NOW: National Health Education Committee, Inc. 1955-67 (Box 114, Folder 53)
    - Foundation, Lalor 1959-74 (Box 114, Folder 54)
    - Lilly Endowment, Inc.
      - 1973-74 (Box 114, Folder 55)
      - 1975-78 (Box 114)
    - Foundations and Funds, M
      - 1966-74 (Box 114, Folder 56)
      - 1975-78 (Box 114)
    - Marmot Foundation from 1970-71 (Box 114, Folder 57)
    - Mellon (The Andrew W.) Foundation (Formerly Avalon Foundation)
      - 1969-74 (Box 114, Folder 58)
      - 1975-77 (Box 114)
    - Merrill (Charles E.) Trust 1968-70 (Box 114, Folder 59)
    - Milbank Memorial Fund, Correspondence 1956-63 (Box 114, Folder 60)
    - Foundations, Miscellaneous Correspondence Pertaining to Foundations (Unspecified) 1961-67 (Box 114, Folder 61)
    - Mobil Foundation, Inc. 1971-74 (Box 114, Folder 62)
    - The Moody Foundation 1968-73 (Box 114, Folder 63)
    - Hugh Moore Fund, Correspondence 1959-72 (Box 114, Folder 64-66)
    - Foundations and Funds, N 1966-74 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - National Foundation/March of Dimes
      - 1963-74 (Box 115, Folder 2)
      - 1975-78 (Box 115)
    - National Science Foundation 1959-61 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Nichols Foundation, Inc. 1971 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - New York Foundation 1963-71 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - New York Fund for Children 1963-64 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Noyes (Jessie Smith) Foundation
      - 1966-74 (Box 115, Folder 7)
      - 1975-79 (Box 115)
    - Foundations and Funds, O 1973-74 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Old Dominion Foundation (Merged Mellon [A.W.] 1969) 1963-68 (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Foundations and Funds, P 1967-74 (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - The Pathfinder Fund 1958-67, undated (Box 115, Folder 11-12)
    - Population Resources Center 1979 (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - Public Welfare Foundations, Inc. 1965-69 (Box 115, Folder 14)
    - Foundations and Funds, Q (Empty) (Box 115, Folder 15)
    - Foundations and Funds, R 1970-74 (Box 115, Folder 16)
    - The Reader's Digest Foundation
      - 1970-74 (Box 115, Folder 17)
      - 1975-78 (Box 115)
    - Richardson (Sid) Foundation 1967-72 (Box 115, Folder 18)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Correspondence
      - 1969-74 (Box 115, Folder 19)
      - 1975-77 (Box 115)
    - The Rockefeller Foundation
      - The President's Review and Annual Report 1967 (Box 115, Folder 20)
      - 1955-74 (Box 115, Folder 21)
      - 1975-77 (Box 115)
    - Rockefeller Family and Associates, Correspondence 1962-68 (Box 115, Folder 22)
    - Foundations and Funds, S
      - 1967-74 (Box 115, Folder 23)
      - 1975 (Box 115)
    - Foundations, Scaife Family
      - Annual Report 1974 (Box 115, Folder 24)
      - Foundations, Scaife Family, T. Mellon and Sons
        - 1970-74 (Box 115, Folder 25)
        - 1975-78 (Box 115)
        - 1965-69 (Box 115, Folder 26)
      - Special Projects Fund
        - 1970-74 (Box 115, Folder 27)
        - 1975-76 (Box 115)
        - Pregnancy Counseling Service, Boston 1971 (Box 115, Folder 28)
      - Mellon and Sons, Regional Medical Consultant Program 1968-71 (Box 115, Folder 29)
    - Searle Foundation 1962-69 (Box 115, Folder 30)
    - Foundation, Sloan, Correspondence 1967-71 (Box 115, Folder 31)
    - Carol Smith Charitable Trust
      - 1970-74 (Box 115, Folder 32)
      - 1975-78 (Box 115)
    - Carol Stewart Smith Trust Fund, Special Trust Fund 1959-61 (Box 115, Folder 33)
    - Stern Family Fund 1963-68 (Box 115, Folder 34)
    - Stott (The Louis L.) Foundation
      - 1971-74 (Box 115, Folder 35)
      - 1975-77 (Box 115)
    - Sunnen, Joseph, Sunnen Foundation
      - Correspondence 1961-65 (Box 115, Folder 36)
      - Library Distribution Project 1965-66 (Box 115, Folder 37)
    - Surdna Foundation, Inc. 1972-74 (Box 115, Folder 38)
    - Foundations and Funds, T 1967-73 (Box 115, Folder 39)
    - Foundations, Tax Legislation, Tax Reform 1969-75 (Box 115, Folder 40)
    - Foundations and Funds, U 1965 (Box 115, Folder 41)
    - Foundations, U.S. Steel Foundation, Inc., Dr. Fred Armstrong 1967-74 (Box 115, Folder 42)
    - Foundations and Funds, V (empty) (Box 115, Folder 43)
    - Van American Foundation 1970-71 (Box 115, Folder 44)
    - Foundations and Funds, W
      - 1966-74 (Box 115, Folder 45)
      - 1975-78 (Box 115)
    - Worcester Foundation, Dr. Gregory Pincus 1955-70 (Box 115, Folder 46)
    - Foundations and Funds, X (empty) (Box 115, Folder 47)
    - Foundations and Funds, Y (empty) (Box 115, Folder 48)
    - Foundations and Funds, Z (empty) (Box 115, Folder 49)
  - Fr, Misc.
    - 1959-74 (Box 115, Folder 50)
    - 1975-79 (Box 115)
  - G, Misc.
    - 1961-74 (Box 115, Folder 51)
    - 1975-79 (Box 115)
  - Gamble, Dr. Clarence J. 1955-63 (Box 115, Folder 52)
  - Gamut Press (Ira Dreyer) 1961-64 (Box 115, Folder 53)
  - Ge, Misc. 1964-69 (Box 115, Folder 54)
  - Genetic Laboratories (Sperm Banks) 1971-72 (Box 115, Folder 55)
  - Genocide 1970-71 (Box 115, Folder 56)
  - Gi, Misc. 1961-68 (Box 115, Folder 57)
  - Gibbons, S.J., Rev. Wm. J. 1958-62 (Box 115, Folder 58)
  - Gl, Misc. (Empty) (Box 115, Folder 59)
  - Go, Misc. 1962-69 (Box 115, Folder 60)
  - Gorman, Mike 1961-65 (Box 115, Folder 61)
  - Gr, Misc.
    - 1959-74 (Box 115, Folder 62)
    - 1975-79 (Box 115)
  - Grants, Applications and Proposals, RFP HSA 240-BCHS-165(8) GJG: Celebrities Media Project to Motivate Adolescents Towards Responsible Sexuality and Parenthood 1978 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Conferences on Teenagers and Family Planning, RFP HSA 240-BCHS-155(6), Submitted by Youth and Student Affairs 1976 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Grants, Applications and Proposals 1976-79 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Grants, Applications and Proposals, RFP HSA 240-BCHS-100(6) (HMD): Clearing House for Family Planning Information and Educational Materials 1976 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Grants, Applications and Proposals
    - 1974 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - 1975 (Box 116)
  - Grants, Applications and Proposals, HSA 240-BCHS-176(5): Development of Patient Education Curriculum Regarding Assessment of Medical Care/Family Planning 1975 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Grants, Applications and Proposals, HSA 240-BCHS-179(5) JET: Family Planning for the Mentally Retarded 1975 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Grants, Application and Proposals, RFP HSA 240-BCHS-195(5) WK: Clearinghouse For Family Planning Information and Educational Materials: A Feasibility Study 1975 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Grants, Applications and Proposals, HSA 240-BCHS-197(5): A Study of Contraceptive Educational Needs of Patients In Family Planning Clinics 1975 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Grants, Applications and Proposals
    - 1974 (Box 116, Folder 10-11)
    - RFP HSA 105-BCHS-196(4) 1974 (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - RFP HSA 105-BCHS-316(4) CLS: Development of Protype Family Planning Information and Education Materials 1974 (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - 1970-1973 (Box 116, Folder 14-17)
    - Project Proposal for Continuation of Research Grant, H-168-1 (C2), Family Planning: Clinic and Cost Evaluation: A Cross-Sectional Clinic Cost Study, Submitted by Eleanor M. Snyder, Ph.D., Director, Department of Research, (two bound sections), circa 1970 (Box 116, Folder 18)
    - 1967-69 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - 1965-70 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence
      - 1971-74 (Box 117, Folder 3)
      - 1975-77 (Box 117)
  - Grants, Policies and Procedures, Dept. HEW Guidelines